Hi, Jenny.
What a surprise.
>> Hi, Steve.
>> How are you? You're looking great.
>> Ah, thanks. I'm well.
How about you?
>> I'm okay.
Hey,
it's starting to rain.
Would you like a coffee?
>> Oh, thanks, Steve, but I have a meeting
in an hour.
>> Oh, come on, Jenny. I'd like to talk to
you.
>> Okay.
A quick coffee.
>> Jenny, I'd
like to ask you something.
>> Yes?
>> There's an exhibition of Picasso at the
MoMA next week. I know you love Picasso.
Would you like to come with me?
>> Listen, Steve, I'm really busy at work
at the moment.
Next week isn't a good week for me.
>> Sure. No problem.
Maybe we can meet one evening
when you have more time and
have dinner or
see a show?
>> Listen, Steve,
I don't think it's a good idea.
But, thanks.
Look at the time.
I need [snorts] to go.
Let's ask for the check.